

Profile

I am an undergraduate in Software Engineering and Management at University of Gothenburg in 2022.

- I am careful, resistant to stress, self-motivated with a strong desire to learn new things and like to take my own initiative.
- I am active, like to cooperate in teamwork for a positive working environment with other colleagues.
- I am open to new ideas and like to listen to advice from experienced colleagues.
- I am looking forward to new challenges and I am convinced that my competence and positive attitude are my biggest advantages.

★ Personal projects

Personal Portfolio

November 2022 — December 2022

My portfolio of my resume of introducing myself, my background, projects and technologies I have learned and used in the past 2022.

Tools: React.js, Next.js, React-icons, styled components

Deploy at: https://zhijiewei.netlify.app

Shanghai kitchen UI/UX application

November 2022 — December 2022

A modern and fully responsive UI/UX restaurant menu application with React.js, React-icons, CSS.

Deploy at: https://shanghai-kitchen.netlify.app

Keep Fit Fitness application

October 2022 — November 2022

A fitness training application that help you browse 1000+ exercises with examples, similar exercises and even much more. You can choose target muscle groups to workout in the gym.

Tools: React.js, React-icons, material-UI, Rapid API

Deploy at: https://keepfit-fitness.netlify.app

Fullstack MERN project

July 2022 — October 2022

A fullstack MERN (Mongodb, ExpressJS, React and NodeJS) application to post a memory, edit, delete and count like button.

Tools: Frontend: use React.js framework, material UI for the styling, call APIs through axios and redux for state management.

Backend: use Express.js framework, Node.js as runtime engine, and connect with mongodb.

Deploy at: https://memories-fullstackapp.netlify.app

Details

Mölndal, 43161 Sweden zjwei0201@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ zhijie-wei-858895219/ GitHub: https://github.com/ZJW-92

Portfolio website: https://zhijiewei.netlify.app

Skills

IBM SPSS Statistics

Jupyter notebook

Tableau

Robot Framework

Python

Selenium

Jenkins

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

React

Vue

Mongodb

Java

R

C++

Languages

Chinese

English

Swedish

Robot Framework Automation exercises

October 2022 — October 2022

Basic web automation testings using Selenium Library and Python in Robot Framework. It includes test cases, mouse actions, buttons, drop down box, data driven testing and connect the repository with Jenkins for CI. In Jenkins, implement basic Jenkins pipeline script and build and implement basic maven project, build and test

Tools: Robot Framework, Selenium, Jenkins, Pycharm

Education

Bachelor of Science within major in Software Engineering and Management, University of Gothenburg, Gothenburg

September 2019 — June 2022

- Experience in an Agile/Scrum development process
- Basic knowledge of testing automation, software quality assurance and DevOps
- Experience of CI/CD tools: GitLab
- Basic database knowledge: MySQL, MongoDB
- Machine Learning and Deep Learning practice with jupyter notebook and python
- Basic applicable development languages: Java, JavaScript, Python.
- Basic web application frontend and framework (e.g. React, Vue) and backend framework (e.g. Django)
- Solid mathematics background: Calculus, Linear algebra etc

Hermods AB and Studium, Gothenburg

September 2018 — May 2020

Passed SFI D. Grade: B. Svenska som andraspråk 1. Grade: E. Svenska som andraspråk 2. Grade: C

Master, Shanghai University of Science and Technology, Shanghai

September 2014 — June 2017

Master degree of Industrial Economics with specializing in SPSS statistical tool.

Exchange student, Högskolan i Borås, Borås

September 2015 — June 2016

Courses: International management, Supply Chain Management and Basic Swedish I and II.

Experience

Chinese to English translator at Shanghai Xinzhi Private Entry-Exit Service Co., Ltd., Shanghai

June 2017 — June 2018

 Organize customers' immigration documents, translate to English and proofread.

Volunteer at Swedish Red Cross, Borås

April 2016 — June 2016

 Move second-hand books, clothes to the warehouse and responsible for cashier.